hey
bunkery's birth was indeed a great
moment of joy for her parents
grandparents uncles and aunts proud papa
ankush was happy super happy but he gets
super worried too he remembers his
colleagues advice being a father is a
matter of great joy but a great
responsibility to look at education for
imagine the amount of money you'll need
23 years from now look at inflation it's
your duty to provide for her how idea
ankush quickly checks smart kid with
icic approved Smart Life a market linked
unit plan specially designed to meet
your child's future needs and he invests
just 5 000 rupees per month in the plan
with a policy term of 23 years in a few
years
proudly sends pankhori to the best
school in town
without a worry of Hefty school fees as
he was already prepared as pankuri grows
into a beautiful smart and confident
young woman she has many dreams to
fulfill many new Skies to fly ankush was
ready to support her dreams with an
investment that was growing with
pancreations
pushes a proud papa once again
happy that he took the right decision at
the right time his timely investment in
smart kid with icic approved Smart Life
unit plan paid
off he can now lean back and relax fully
confident of his daughter's future as
the plan will take care of her dreams
and ambitions even when he is not there
anymore
[Music]
just like ankush you can also secure
your child's future by investing in
smart kid with icic approved Smart Life
buying smart kid with icic approve Smart
Life online is safe secure and
convenient it also comes with the
benefit of one percent discount on
premium allocation chart and what's more
you can enjoy tax benefits too start
planning for your child's future today
visit www.icsaprolife.com